Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Collection
State University of New York at Oswego
- VI. Environment, 1964 - 1979
  - Environmental Quality, 1972-1965, 1965 - 1972 (Box-folder 13-03)
    Environment Environmental Quality, 1972-1965 Publications: national; reports: state; clippings: material from New York State Department of Environmental Conservation; OVLWV program material
  - Pollution control, 1977-1968, 1968 - 1977 (Box-folder 13-04)
    Environment Pollution control, 1977-1968 Correspondence; OVLWV program materials; workshop program; clippings
  - Pollution control, clippings, 1970-1969, 1969 - 1970 (Box-folder 13-05)
    Environment Pollution control, clippings, 1970-1969 Clippings and magazine articles
  - Oswego River Basin, n.d. (Box-folder 13-06)
    Environment Oswego River Basin
  - Barge Canal, n.d. (Box-folder 13-07)
    Environment Barge Canal
- VII. Energy, 1969 - 1979
  - Energy, general, 1973 - 1977 (Box-folder 14-01)
    Energy, general 1977-1973 Clippings
  - League of Women Voters, 1977-1976, 1976 - 1977 (Box-folder 14-02)
    Energy League of Women Voters, 1977-1976 Publications: national; reports: state, Syracuse League of Women Voters; correspondence; material on OVLWV activities
  - League of Women Voters, 1975-1974, 1974 - 1975 (Box-folder 14-03)
    Energy League of Women Voters, 1975-1974 Publications: national; reports: state, Syracuse League of Women Voters; correspondence; material on OVLWV activities
  - Nuclear, 1979-1969, 1969 - 1979 (Box-folder 14-04)
    Energy Nuclear, 1979-1969 Clippings: national, local, state; correspondence; OVLVW program material; non-league publications; publications: Syracuse League of Women Voters
  - Conservation, 1978-1974, 1974 - 1978 (Box-folder 14-05)
    Energy Conservation, 1978-1974 Correspondence; clippings; publications: national; OVLWV material; material from Niagara-Mohawk Power Company and St. Lawrence River and Eastern Ontario Commission
  - League of Women Voters skits, 1977 (Box-folder 14-06)
    Energy League of Women Voters skits, 1977 Material prepared by various local League of Women Voters chapters; correspondence
  - Cooperative Extension seminar, 1977 (Box-folder 14-07)
    Energy Cooperative Extension seminar, 1977 Correspondence; non-league published material; publicity clippings; material gathered for cooperative education seminar
- Collection Addition- 1980, 1967 - 1979
  - I- Environment, 1971 - 1976
    - A. Oswego, 1976
      - Oswego River Drainage Basin, n.d. (Box-folder 15-01)
        Environment - Oswego
      - Oswego Water Quality Committee Minutes, May, 1976 - July, 1976 (Box-folder 15-02)
        Environment - Oswego Oswego Water Quality Committee Minutes July 1976 through May 1976
    - B. Fulton, n.d.
      - Report on proposed source of water for Fulton, n.d. (Box-folder 15-03)
        Environment- Fulton Report on proposed source of water for Fulton
    - C. County, 1971
      - CNY Water Quality Management Program, n.d. (Box-folder 15-04)
        Environment - County CNY Water Quality Management Program
      - Oswego County Environmental Plan, n.d. (Box-folder 15-05)
      - CNY Water Quality Management Project, n.d. (Box-folder 15-06)
        Environment - County CNY Water Quality Management Project
      - Oswego County Water Quality Management Sub-plan, n.d. (Box-folder 15-07)
        Environement - County Oswego County Water Quality Management Subplan
      - Municipal Wastewaters Project: Oswego County, n.d. (Box-folder 15-08)
        Environment - County Municipal Wastewaters Project: Oswego County
      - Oswego County Component: CNY Water Quality Management Project, n.d. (Box-folder 15-09)
        Environment - County Oswego County Component: CNY Water Quality Management Project
      - Oswego County 208 Water Committee Repor, n.d. (Box-folder 15-10)
        Environment - County Oswego County 208 Water Committee Report
      - Paper: Coastal Management Program, n.d. (Box-folder 15-11)
        Environment - County Paper: Coastal Management Program
      - Summary Environmental Report, October, 1971 (Box-folder 15-12)
        Environment - County Summary Environmental Report October 1971
      - CNY 208 Project: Watershed Delineation, n.d. (Box-folder 15-13)
        Environment - County CNY 208 Project: Watershed Delineation
      - Revision to CNY Control Program, n.d. (Box-folder 15-14)
        Environment - County Revision to CNY Control Program
      - Water Quality Problem Areas, n.d. (Box-folder 15-15)
        Environment - County Water Quality Problem Areas
      - Maps – Coastal Boundary Program (Box-folder 15-16)
        Environment - County Maps - Coastal Boundary Program
      - Suggestive Task for County Level Water Committee, n.d. (Box-folder 15-17)
        Environment - County Suggestive Task for County Level Water Committee
    - D. St. Lawrence – Eastern Ontario Commission, n.d.
      - Technical Memorandum (Box-folder 15-18)
        Environment - St. Lawrence-Eastern Ontario Commission Technical memorandum
      - Technical Report on Population, Labor Force and the Economy (Box-folder 15-19)
        Environment - St. Lawrence-Eastern Ontario Commission Technical report on Population, Labor Force and the Economy
      - General Goals and Objectives for Coastal Resources Development (Box-folder 16-01)
        Environment - St. Lawrence-Eastern Ontario Commission General Goals and Objectives for Coastal Resources Development
      - Technical Report on Geology, n.d. (Box-folder 16-02)
        Environment - St. Lawrence-Eastern Ontario Commission Technical report on geology
      - Technical Report on Soils, n.d. (Box-folder 16-03)
        Environment - St. Lawrence-Eastern Ontario Commission Technical report on soils
  - II- Government, 1967 - 1978
    - A. General, 1967
      - Proposed legislation for John R. Zagame, n.d. (Box-folder 16-04)
        Government - General Proposed legislation for John R. Zagame
      - Education and the 1967 Constitutional Convention (Box-folder 16-05)
        Government - General Education and the 1967 Constitutional Convention
      - Proposed NYS Constitution, 1967 (Box-folder 16-06)
        Government - General Proposed NYS Constitution, 1967
    - B. Local, 1976 - 1978
      - The Summary Master Plan (Fulton), n.d. (Box-folder 16-07)
        Government - General The Summary Master Plan. Fulton
      - Zoning Ordinance (Hastings), n.d. (Box-folder 16-08)
        Government - Local Zoning Ordinance. Hastings
      - Comprehensive Development Plan (Volney), n.d. (Box-folder 16-09)
        Government - Local Comprehensive Development Plan. Volney
      - Oswego County Area Subcommittee’s Tentative Schedules, n.d. (Box-folder 16-10)
        Government - Local Oswego County Area Subcommittee's Tentative Schedules
      - Memos and Correspondence, Oswego Planning Board, 1976 - 1978 (Box-folder 16-11)
        Government - Local Memos and correspondence, Oswego Planning Board January - March 1976
      - Outlines and Public Notices (Box-folder 16-12)
        Government - Local Outlines and Public Notices
      - Maps of Wards and Districts, 1976 (Box-folder 16-13)
        Government - Local Maps of wards and districts Oswego and Fulton, 1976
      - Analysis of the Community (Fulton), n.d. (Box-folder 16-14)
        Government - Local Analysis of the Community. Fulton
  - III- Periodicals, 1975 - 1979
    - Central New York Environment, 1975 - 1979 (Box-folder 16-15)
      Periodicals Central New York Environment June 1979 through June 1975
    - Coastliners, 1978 - 1979 (Box-folder 16-16)
      Periodicals Coastliners July 1979 through January 1978
  - IV- General, n.d.
    - Correspondence to L. Jackim (Box-folder 16-17)
      General Correspondence to L. Jackim
    - Ephemera, n.d. (Box-folder 16-18)
      General Ephemera
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box-folder 16-19)
      General Miscellaneous
- Collection Addition- 1984, 1972 - 1977
  - I. Other county charters, 1973 - 1976
    - Other County Charters, 1973 + n.d. (Box-folder 17-01)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government 1972-1979 Other county Charters 1. Chemung County - local law no. 4, 1973 - charter 2. Monroe County - charter, 1973 3. Tompkins County (a portion of charter, n.d.)
    - Correspondence, 1974 - 1976 (Box-folder 17-02)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government Other county charters Correspondence. July 1976 - June 12, 1974 List of charters adopted since September 1969
  - II. Local County Government, 1974 - 1977
    - Correspondence of President of League, 1975 - 1977 (Box-folder 17-03)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government Local County Government Correspondence of president of league, 1975-1979 a. press releases, 1975 b. notes for a radio talk
    - Clippings, 1974 - 1977 (Box-folder 17-04)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government Clippings, March-April 1977 --- May 1974 Including organizational chart; statements of what charter government is, 1972-1977
    - Clippings, 1975 - 1977 (Box-folder 17-05)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government Clippings, 1975-1977
  - III. League happenings, 1973 - 1976
    - Position papers, 1975 (Box-folder 17-06)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government League happenings Position papers - July 15, 1975; June 3, 1975; January 22, 1975. Consensus questionairre - February 20, 1975; clippings; blank forms. Comments to league re: charter
    - Meetings and workshops, 1973 - 1975 (Box-folder 17-07)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government League happenings Meetings and workshops. September 17, 1975 -- November 6-7, 1973 Materials for programs
    - Plans for County Meetings, 1976 (Box-folder 17-08)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government League happenings Plans for County Meetings, 1976
    - Meetings and workshops, 1976 (Box-folder 17-09)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government League happenings Meetings and workshops, 1976 Shakespeare Club, Fulton Monday History Club, Pulaski
    - Oswego County Cooperative Extension, 1976 (Box-folder 17-10)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government League happenings Oswego County Cooperative Extension, 1976 "A candidate - how to be one or back one"
  - IV. Civil Service Commission, 1973 - 1977
    - Civil Service Commission, 1975 - 1976 (Box-folder 17-11)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government Civil Service Commission Civil Service Commission - Rules for the classified civil service of Oswego County. James Wright, Director, 1975-1976
    - Civil Service Personnel, 1973 - 1977 (Box-folder 17-12)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government Civil Service Commission Civil Service - Personnel Directories; rules of Bod of Supervisors, Oswego County and Oswego County Legislature. List of standing committees, 1973 - 1977
  - County Legislature, 1973 - 1977
    - Directory, 1973 - 1977 (Box-folder 17-13)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government County Legislature Directory; lists of legislators, 1973-1977; correspondence, 1975- Clippings, December 1974 -- December 1977 Government Committee meeting minutes. June 1973 - December 1974
    - County Budget, 1976 - 1977 (Box-folder 17-14)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government County Legislature County Budget Pamphlet, "The Citizen and the budget process: opening up the system" Correspondence Tentative budget for 1977 from auditor Tentative budget for 1977 from legislative chairman Proposed budget for 1976 Budget information for 1976 form Director or Personnel Budget information for 1976 from Commissioner of Social Services
    - County Budget, 1974 (Box-folder 18-01)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government County Legislature County budget, 1974 Miscellaneous information concerning the makeup of 1974 budget
    - County Budget, 1973 (Box-folder 18-02)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government County Legislature County budget - 1973
    - County Budgets, 1975 - 1977 (Box-folder 18-03)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government County Legislature County Budgets Press clippings on 1975, 1976, 1977 Press clippings on Surplus, 1977
  - Personnel, 1966 - 1977
    - Civil Service Commission, n.d. (Box-folder 18-04)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government Personnel Civil Service Commission Correspondence between administrator and league president Correspondence between chairman of legislature and league president
    - Contract agreements, 1966 - 1974 (Box-folder 18-05)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government Personnel Four contract agreements Between Oswego County and CSEA, Oswego County Employees Unit. "Clarification of Managerial and Confidential Status" New York State Employee's Retirement System pamphlets: "Benefits - Career plan", pre-July 1, 1973 members. "Disability benefits, 1974". "Your options at retirement, 1966". "What is the Taylor Law? and how does it work?" "The Taylor Law", 1974 Clippings, 1974-1977 on Personnel, CSEA and Civil Service
    - Meetings, January, 1977 - May, 1977 (18-06)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government Personnel Meetings January 1977 - May 12, 1977
    - Meetings, 1976 (Box-folder 18-07)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government Personnel Meetings January 1976 - December 1976
    - Meetings, 1973 (Box-folder 18-08)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government Personnel Meetings January 8, 1973 - December 1973
    - Miscellaneous general county information, n.d. (Box-folder 18-09)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government Personnel Miscellaneous general county information
    - County Government, 1971 - 1977 (Box-folder 18-10)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government Personnel County Government Charter Working File, 1971- 1977
    - County Government, 1974 - 1977 (Box-folder 18-11)
      Oswego Valley League of Women Voters Study of County Government Personnel County Government Structure, Function, 1974-1977 Clippings, 1976-1978
    - County Government, 1975 - 1976 (Box-folder 18-12)